

Md. Rohul Amin

Software Engineer

Sha 66/3, Shadhinata Sarani, North Badda, Gulshan, Dhaka, Bangladesh 🛗 05 Jan 1996

🟲 Bangladeshi 🕲 Unmarried in radipu 🕜 radipu 🖹 radipu 🔇 dipuxoo Bē radipu

radipu.me 🖒 radipu

CAREER OBJECTIVES

I am a graduate with a bachelor's degree in Computer Science and Engineering. I am experienced in both front-end and back-end programming languages. Now, I am looking for establishing my career as a .NET developer. I am a quick learner and willing to learn new technologies to upgrade myself with time. I am working with .NET technology since 2018.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Jan 2022 Software Engineer
Dhaka, Bangladesh CureTech Ltd

Aug 2021 - Jan 2022Software EngineerSunderland, EnglandGinilab Limited ☑

Ginilab is a software development company based in Sunderland, Tyne & Wear, UK. Over the last few years, they've made a reputation for building software that looks great and is easy to use. Currently, I worked there with .NET Framework, DevExpress, WinForms, Software Design, Fronend, and Back-end.

Feb 2021 – Jul 2021 Software Engineer

Dhaka, Bangladesh OurEdu

OurEdu provides web-based software for educational institutions. I have had working here with C# ASP.NET Core 3.1, JavaScript, Bootstrap, jQuery, LINQ, CSS, MSSQL, DevOps.

PROJECTS

Feb 2022 - present Bachao ☑

Against the rape

It's a mobile application platform where a victim can seek help during and after the incident. The backend was developed with .NET. Technology Used: .NET5, Angular, WebAPI, MSSQL Aug 2021 – Jan 2022 Restaurant Management System

It's a desktop software, mostly used in the UK and in the middle east. Nearly 200+ restaurants and thousands of customers use this software for ordering food inside and outside the restaurant.

Technology Used: ASP.NET, DevExpress, WinForms, MySQL, Laragon, HeidiSQL

Feb 2021 - May 2021 Account Management System for Shidlai Ashraf Secondary School

Technology Used: C#, ASP.NET Core 3.1, JavaScript, Bootstrap, CSS, jQuery, JSON, LINQ, and following by Onion Architecture.

May 2019 - Aug 2019 Library Management System

Technology Used: C#, ASP.NET Core 2.1, Bootstrap, CSS, jQuery, JSON, LINQ.

SKILLS

Programming

Language

C, C++, Java, JavaScript, C#, R, Python, TypeScript, Go

Backend Development

.NET Core, .NET, NodeJS, Laravel

DevOps

AWS, GCP, Azure, Docker, Jenkins, Kubernetes, Bash

Data Structure and Algorithm

Cyber Security

Penetration, Forensics, Reverse Engineering, Social Engineering **Frontend**

Development

VueJS, Angular, HTML5, AngularJS, Bootstrap3, 4, CSS3, Sass

Database

Oracle, MySQL, MSSQL Server, PostgreSQL

Source Control

Git, GitHub

Interpersonal skills —

Listening, Caring, Leadership, Self-Motivated, Responsibility, Teamwork

EDUCATION

May 2021 Bachelor of Science in Computer Science and Engineering

Dhaka, Bangladesh International University of Business Agriculture and Technology

Completed BSc with a CGPA of 3.27 out of 4.00

Jul 2011 - Aug 2013 Higher Secondary Certificate

Dhaka, Bangladesh Cambrian College

Completed HSC with a GPA of 5.00 out of 5.00

Jan 2009 – May 2011 Cumilla, Bangladesh

Secondary School Certificate

Shidlai Ashraf Secondary School

Completed SSC with a GPA of 5.00 out of 5.00

✓ INTERESTS

• Learning New Skills

• Public Speaking

• Reading

Writing

♦ LANGUAGES

Bangla • • • • English • • • •